Guide to the Gwilym A. Price Papers, 1917-1983 AIS.2008.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1957-1983; XII.
  - Professional life, 1957-1983; 1.
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, Dinner honoring [Donald] Burnham, January 29, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Westinghouse South Africa Trip Photo Album, August 1959 (Box 13, Volume 2)
    - Westinghouse China Trip Photo Album, October 1962 (Box 13, Volume 3)
    - Westinghouse Russia Trip Photo Album, 1958 (Box 14, Volume 1)
    - Westinghouse Japan Trip Photo Album, c 1962 (Box 14, Volume 2)
    - Eastman Kodak Company, Board of Directors Meeting., November 19, 1964 (Box 15, Volume 2)
  - Fishing and Hunting Trips, 1972-1978; 2.
    This subseries contains photographs and photo albums from Price's fishing and hunting trips in the U.S. and abroad, many with other corporate executives. Most photographs are candid shots.
    - Hunting trip, Nairobi, Kenya, c 1960 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Fishing Trip, Copper River, Alaska, September 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Fishing trip, Deep Water Cay, Bahamas, c 1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Fishing trip, Deep Water Cay, Bahamas, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Fishing trip, Anticosti Island, Quebec, Canada, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Fishing trip, Casa Mar, Costa Rica, c 1977 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Fishing trip, Anticosti Island, Quebec, Canada, c 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Fishing trip, Iceland, c 1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Fishing trip, Deep Water Cay, Bahamas, c 1970 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Fishing trip, Unknown location, c 1970 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - "Lion Hunting in the Arctic?," altered photograph, c 1970 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Family and personal photographs, 1958-1980; 3.
    This subseries largely consists of photographs of Price's children and grandchildren, many of whom are not identified by name.
    - Gwilym and Marion Price, photo negatives, c 1958 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Family photographs, 1970-1980 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Realia, 1960-1979; XIII.
  - Flag, originally with Price's honorable discharge, 1917 (Box 15, Item 1)
  - Coin, Christening of the U.S.S. Enterprise, September 24, 1960 (Box 15, Item 2)
  - Pin, Pinebloom Plantation, c1970 (Box 15, Item 3)
  - Plaque, Lifetime membership in the Defenders Club of the Second Amendment Foundation, October 10, 1979 (Box 15, Item 4)
    Series contains four artifacts related to various timeperiods of Price's life, including his militrary service, travel, and professional life.
- Audiovisual materials, 1955-1980; XIV.
  Most of the items in this series are film of Price's hunting and fishing trips. Series also contains brief audio of a speech Price made when accepting the Lord & Taylor Award, a film on atomic energy for which Price was interviewed, and several commercial audiocassettes.
  - Audio Materials, 1957-1975; 1.
    Brief audio of Price's remarks at an award banquet and a commercially-pressed cassette of the Westinghouse chorale.
    - "Lord & Taylor Award: Gwilym A. Price," 7-inch analog audio disc, one-sided, 1957 (Box 16, Disc 1)
    - Christmas Collection. Dorothy Kudoke Mulranan, soprano; Barry O'Toole, saxophone; Westinghouse Chorale. Audiocassette., c 1980 (Box 16, Cassette 1)
  - Film, 1955-1973; 2.
    Film, largely from Price's fishing trips. Unless otherwise noted, all film is 16mm.
    - Atlantic Salmon Fishing Master Recording, Anticosti Island, Quebec, Canada, 1955 (Box 16, Reel 1)
    - "Trip to Moosonee," Ontario, Canada, c 1959 (Box 16, Reel 2)
    - Atlantic Salmon Fishing, Anticosti Island, Quebec, Canada, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Reel 3)
    - Atlantic Salmon Fishing, Anticosti Island, Quebec, Canada, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Reel 4)
    - Atlantic Salmon Fishing, Anticosti Island, Quebec, Canada, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Reel 5)
    - Atlantic Salmon Fishing, Anticosti Island, Quebec, Canada, c 1960 (Box 16, Reel 6)
    - "Space Age Success Formula" from the Focal Point series, Westinghouse Broadcasting Co./KDKA Television, 1963 (Box 16, Reel 7)
    - Far East Trip, 1963 (Box 16, Reel 8)
    - Atlantic Salmon Fishing, Anticosti Island, Quebec, Canada, 1973 (Box 16, Reel 9)